# **ALI HAIDAR**

COMPUTER TEACHER & DEVELOPER



+92-315-4846093



alihaidar158008@gmail.com



G.M. Abad Faisalabad , Punjab

## **About Me**

Dedicated and passionate Computer Teacher & developer with 2 years of experience in effectively educating students on computer science concepts and applications. Seeking a position to inspire and empower students to develop strong computational thinking skills and excel in the digital world.

## **Experience**

### The Skills institute of IT training & development

APR. 2023 - Current React & React Native Developer

Redet & Redet Halive Developer

### Minhaj-ul-Quran Model Secondary school

FEB. 2023 - Current Computer Teacher

### The Skills institute of IT training & development

MAR 2022 - JAN. 2023 Python Developer & Instructor

#### Payam-Bar Academy of Science & Arts

OCT. 2021 - JAN. 2023 Computer Teacher

#### **Avid Academy of Science & Arts**

AUG. 2021 - OCT. 2021 Computer Teacher

## **Education**

#### 2020-2024

Govt. Postgraduate College of Science Samanabad

### **BS** Computer Science

## Language

Punjabi

Urdu

English

## **Expertise**

- React
- React Native
- Firebase
- Python
- Web Scrapping

## Reference

Reference will be furnished on demand